演唱：Avicii
Wake Me Up
唤醒我
压制:随Feng
Feeling my way through the darkness
我在黑暗中摸索前行
Wake Me Up
Guided by a beating heart
遵循心灵的引导
I can't tell where the journey will end
我不知道哪里是旅行的终点
But I know where to start
但我明白是从何处开始的
They tell me I'm too young to understand
人们说我太年轻不需要明白
They say I'm caught up in a dream
他们说我只是沉迷于梦境中
Well life will pass me by if I don't open up my eyes
如果我不睁开双眼 我的人生将会蹉跎而过
Well that's fine by me
对此我没意见
So wake me up when it's all over
所以当一切结束时叫醒我
When I'm wiser and I'm older
当我成熟时
All this time I was finding myself
这些时光我都在找寻自我
And I didn't know I was lost
此时我并不知道我已迷失自己
So wake me up when it's all over
所以 当一切结束时叫醒我
When I'm wiser and I'm older
当我成熟时
All this time I was finding myself
所有时光我都在找寻自己
And I didn't know I was lost
但我不知道其实我已迷失自己
I tried carrying the weight of the world
我试图承载世界的责任
But I only have two hands
但我只有双手
Hope I get the chance to travel the world
我希望有机会去环游世界
But I don't have any plans
但我没有个可行的计划
Wish that I could stay forever this young
我希望青春常驻
Not afraid to close my eyes
不用害怕闭上双眼
Life's a game made for everyone
对于任何人来说生活就是一场游戏
And love is the prize
爱情即是游戏的奖赏
So wake me up when it's all over
所以当一切结束的时候唤醒我
When I'm wiser and I'm older
当我成熟的时候
All this time I was finding myself
在此时间段我都在找寻自我
And I didn't know I was lost
但我并不知道其实我已迷失
So wake me up when it's all over
所以当一切终结时唤醒我
When I'm wiser and I'm older
当我成熟的时候
All this time I was finding myself
这之前我都在找寻自己
And I didn't know I was lost
但我并不知道我已迷失
Didn't know I was lost
并不知道我已迷失自己
I didn't know I was lost
我不知道我已迷失自己
I didn't know
我不清楚
压制:随Feng